Good morning!
おっはよーん
It's 8:15 on November 5th!
１１月５日　８時１５分
Tsunemori Akane, your Psycho-Pass Hue is powder blue this morning!
けさの常守朱さんのサイコパス色相はパウダーブルー
Have a wonderful day with that healthy mind of yours!
健康な精神で素晴らしい一日を楽しんでね
Oh man, I messed up...
やっちゃった
Dare ni mo miserarenai mono
My head is full of things
Atama no naka afurete
That I can never tell anybody of
In this perfect world
Machigai sae mo nai sekai he
I roam, a lost being
Mayoikonderu
Arienai hodo surikomareteru
This world is impossibly hard on me
It's an illusion that plays out before my eyes
Me ni mieru mono dake no "sekai" genshou
Abakidaseru kana
Can I find its faults?
Plastic tac tic
Plastic, all is plastic
Mou dare mo okashiku narenai yo
Nobody is allowed to be insane
Kisama mo plastic beautiful world
You're made of plastic too, like this beautiful world
In this beautiful world
Utsukushi sugiru sekai ni
Boku wa nazeka
There is something
Hikari ga mienakute
That obscures all light for me
Haretsu shite yuku kokoro ga
My heart tries to break out
And finds no answer
Mugen no rifurekushon
Secret kills for you
Secret remains for you
The secret remains for you
Don't show me a dark future
Misekake no iro to
Mirai wo abakanai de
Nor a world of pretense
Keep it secret motion
Keep our motion secret
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 翼叔   校对:西西   后期:时末
I'm not on the day shift today... right?
You're meeting up with Funahara Yuki and
Minase Kaori at Akebonobashi Station at 11:00.
今日って日勤じゃないよね
At 14:30, you start second shift duty at the Public Safety Bureau.
１１時から船原ゆきさま 水無瀬佳織さまと曙橋駅で待ち合わせ
１４時３０分より公安局で第二当直勤務でーす
Oh, that's right.
あ～　そっか
What's your room preference today?
今日のお部屋はどうします
Victor Horta's Hotel Tassel.
ヴィクトール·オルタで ホテル·タッセル
Okay! I'll use the library as reference!
はーい　ライブラリ参照しまーす
#02: Those Capable
Your dietary intake yesterday was 2200 kilocalories in total.
「昨日の食事摂取量は合計２，２００キロカロリー」
The recommended amount for today's breakfast is 240 kilocalories.
「今日の朝ご飯は２４０キロカロリーが適正でーす」
I'll have a 200 kilocalorie Chinese-flavored breakfast.
２００キロカロリー  テイストはチャイニーズで
Certainly!
「かしこまりました」
It was my very first day on the job...
配属初日でさ
Why me? What'd I do?
何でよ
もう…
Today's weather will be morning clouds giving way to sunny skies.
今日の天気は曇り後晴れ
There is a 0% chance of precipitation.
降水確率は０％
The anticipated group stress in the Shinjuku ward is Level 3.
新宿区で予測される集団ストレスはレベル３
I recommend taking a supplement to prevent mental contamination.
心理汚染の予防サプリがお勧めです
I guess this'll do.
こんなとこかな
All right, see you later.
じゃあ　行ってくるね
Take care!
お気を付けて～
So...
で…
You messed up, huh?
やらかしちゃったわけだ
Yeah... though I can't give you the details
公安局の仕事なんで
since I work for the Public Safety Bureau and all.
詳しいことは言えないけど
I don't know much about these things,
よく分かんないけどさ
but what you did wasn't in violation of your duties, right?
それはあんたの役職に許されていることなんでしょ
I guess not.
まあね
Then you don't have to worry about it, right?
じゃあ　気に病むことないじゃない
Besides, your Psycho-Pass isn't that clouded either.
サイコパスだってそんなに曇ってないし
I guess that means you're not that bothered by it after all?
案外本当は平気なんじゃないの
C'mon, don't be mean!
え～　そんな
I didn't get a wink of sleep last night.
ゆうべは全然眠れなかったのに
I'm surprised the Hue Check showed such a clear
color for you, considering what you went through.
それだけ悩んでおいて
色相チェックはクリアカラーなんだもんね　朱は
You don't give yourself much psychological care,
感情ケアなんてほとんどやってないくせに
and yet you're such a mental beauty.
すごい　メンタル美人
How do you stay so healthy?
あんたって 何でそんなに健康でいられるの
Well... Maybe I'm just thick-skinned, you know?
まあその…　鈍感なのかな
God really is unfair.
神様ってホント不公平
You said it.
そうそう
I-In any case... It's not that I doubt the Sibyl System,
で…でもさ　シビュラシステムを疑うわけじゃないけど
but I wonder if a career at the
Public Safety Bureau is really right for me.
公安局のキャリアなんて 私に向いてるのかな
Jeez, you're lucky to even have the choice!
カア～　ぜいたくな悩み
I know you like to speak without
thinking, but that's pushing it even for you!
天然でそういうこと 言うかな～まったく
To start with, you were found to have an aptitude for jobs
だいたいさ　朱ってば
at the Ministry of Economy and the Ministry of Technology,
経済省や科学技術省の適性だって出てたのに
and yet you rejected them both and
picked the Public Safety Bureau, right?
それ全部蹴って公安局選んだんでしょ
The best I could do was C-rank scores across the board.
私なんてＣ判定しかもらえなかったのにね
What's the problem? You're good at blue-collar work.
いいじゃん　あんた体動かす仕事は得意なんだから
I'm a systems engineer, so my shoulders are always killing me.
私なんてＳＥよ
もう　肩凝ってしょうがないんだから
Akane, you were an honor student
who scored 700 points on the last exam.
朱はさ　最終考査でポイント７００たたき出した優等生じゃない
You should be able to take on any job with ease, right?
どんな仕事だって チョチョイのチョイでしょ
Sorry. I guess we went a little too far.
ごめんね ちょっとからかい過ぎた
But I think that if anyone can pull off that job, it's you.
でもね　朱ならきっとやり通せる仕事だと思うよ
And not just because of the aptitude the System indicated.
それはシステムが出した適性だけじゃない
As a friend, I know you'll do well.
友人としての直感
"That which needs to be done is
carried out by those capable of doing it.
「成しうる者が為すべきを為す」
Such is the grace bestowed upon mankind by Sibyl."
「これこそシビュラが人類にもたらした恩寵である」
Just kidding.
なんちってね～
Excuse me!
すみません
Is Analyst Karanomori Shion here?
分析官の唐之杜志恩さんはこちらに
Yeah, yeah. Who are you?
はいはい
どちらさま
I'm Tsunemori Akane. I've been assigned to the CID as of yesterday.
昨日付けで刑事課に配属になりました　常守朱です
Oh! You're the new Inspector who shot Shinya, aren't you?
ああ　慎也君を撃った新任監視官って あなたね
Wow... You're a lot cuter than I thought.
へえ～　思ってたよりずっとカワイイ子
That cute face of yours hides how daring you can be, though!
顔に似合わず 思い切ったことするもんね
What happened? Did Shinya grab your butt or something?
何があったの
慎也君にお尻でも触られた
No. Um...
いえ　その
I was told I should come to you to find out how he's doing.
狡噛さんの容体 ここに来れば分かるって聞いて
Oh, that.
ああ　それね
While I do have a physician's license,
いくら医師免許持ってるからって
can you believe that's all it took for the government
to delegate employee health care to the Analysis Lab?
分析室に健康管理まで任せるお役所って　どう思う
Sure, I may be a latent criminal too,
そりゃ　私も潜在犯ですけど
but that doesn't mean they can just
slave drive me as much as they want, right?
だからって　いくらでも便利にこき使っていいって法はないでしょ
R-Right...
Let's see. Akane, was it?
えっと あなた朱ちゃん…だっけ
If you're an Inspector, that puts you
on the fast track at the Bureau, right?
監視官なら 公安局の出世コースでしょ
Hurry up and become a high-ranking official so you can reform the system.
さっさと偉くなっちゃって組織改革してちょうだいよ
You can start by splashing out for a
swimming pool and bar lounge at the CID.
まずは 刑事課備え付けのプールとバーラウンジをこしらえるところから
I'm counting on you!
お願い
Right, well... How's Kougami's treatment going?
いや　そのですね
狡噛さんの治療って
Oh, that's right.
あっ　そうね
Well, you scored a direct hit on his spinal cord,
まあ　脊髄にいい感じに直撃かましてくれたからね
so he's still out of commission.
まだ本調子ってわけにはいかないわ
It'll be a little longer before he's
able to stand, talk, or anything like that.
立ったり　しゃべったりはちょっとね
Of course, you wouldn't be able to join him in bed right now, either.
もちろん　ベッドのお供も無理
If you just want to peek in on him, that'd be okay.
顔だけでも見ていきたいっていうんなら
面会ぐらい大丈夫だけど
What do you wanna do?
どうする
W-Well, I'd better not bother him.
いえ　それなら別に
If he spends today resting, the aftereffects should go away.
今日一日安静にしてれば後遺症も抜けるわよ
Come back tomorrow morning.
またあしたの朝にでもいらっしゃい
Okay.
はい
Latent Criminal Pursuit & Apprehension
Enforce-At-Will Authority Granted
Casualty
Report
After carrying out lethal enforcement on Ookura, he pursued a new enforcement target. Incapacitated by Inspector Tsunemori's Paralyzer.
After being taken hostage by Ookura and released, lethal enforcement was authorized. Currently hospitalized.
After his Criminal Coefficient rose to over 300, lethal enforcement was authorized. Died at the scene.
Work Type
Shimazu Chika
Kougami Shinya (Enforcer, Public Safety Bureau)
Ookura Nobuo
Latent Criminal Pursuit & Apprehension
Enforce-At-Will Authority Granted
Accompanying
Enforcer:
Work Type
Chief Investigator: Nobuchika Ginoza
Weather
Fine
Location of Incident
Date of Incident
Police Details
Director of the Criminal Investigation Division
Accident Report for PSB Vehicles and Officers
KT building, warehouse along the shore
Vicinity of Tokyo, 13th Jurisdiction Control Area, 6th District
Oct. 4th, around 3:30pm
Tomomi Masaoka
Huh?
Um...
あの
Hmm?
Excuse me, are there any other tablets?
すみません
タブレットって他にあります
Enforcer Kougami is using the spare equipment.
備品の予備は狡噛執行官が使用中でーす
But, um... Isn't Kougami...
でも　その…狡噛さんは…
...undergoing treatment after taking a Paralyzer on the chin? Yep!
パラライザーで撃たれて治療中でーす
Ow!
That hurt...
痛え…
Here.
これ
Use this.
使って
O-Okay.
はっ　はい
Sorry for getting in late.
悪ぃ悪ぃ　遅くなって
Oh? You're on duty tonight, young lady?
ってあれ 今日の宿直ってお嬢ちゃん
Ah, yes.
あっ　はい
It must be tough after what happened yesterday.
昨日の今日で大変だね
Well, let's hope that today's a little quieter—
まあ 平和な一日になるよう祈って
This is an elevated Area Stress Level warning.
エリアストレス　上昇警報
A Psycho-Pass above the regulation value has been detected
足立区 伊興グライスヒル内部にて
inside Iko Gryce Hill in the Adachi ward.
規定値超過サイコパスを計測
Inspector on duty, please accompany the Enforcers to the site immediately.
当直監視官は執行官を伴い
直ちに現場へ直行してください
And just when I was hoping today would be quiet...
言ってるそばからそれかよ
Well, our shift just ended, so... good luck.
まあ　俺らはシフト明けっすから
頑張って
Would you like me to cover for Kougami?
狡噛の穴　私が埋めます？
No, that won't be necessary.
いや　何　それには及ばんさ
Let's get going, Ms. Inspector.
さっ　出動だぜ　監視官殿
What?!
Drones have been watching the entrances
to the mall since the warning was triggered.
モール内の出入り口は
警報直後から ドローンが監視してる
They haven't caught anyone yet.
そっちに引っ掛かった獲物はなし
In other words, whoever's elevating
the Area Stress level is still in the mall.
つまり　ここのエリアストレスを高めてる張本人は
まだモールの中にいる
Are we going to use Dominators?
ドミネーターを使うんですか
We'll have them delivered to us as a precaution.
用心のために運ばせはするが…
but we probably won't need them.
まあ　抜くまでのことにはなるまいよ
Well then, shall we go?
そんじゃまあ　行こうかね
Do you feel uncomfortable?
落ち着かねえか？
I thought your generation was used to playing with holo-suits on.
お嬢ちゃんぐらいの年ならホロスーツで遊ぶのなんて慣れっこだろ
It feels a bit weird with my whole body as an Avatar.
全身アバターに成りきるってのはちょっと…
It's okay, so let me see.
大丈夫
Oh, stop it.
あ～やめてってちょっと
Not a chance!
やめないよ
Oh, there's our man.
あ～あれだ
On the right, hiding behind the front column.
右　手前の柱の陰
But... How can you tell without even using a scanner?
そんな…スキャナーも使わずにどうして
A beast can sniff out another beast's scent.
ケダモノはケダモノのにおいを嗅ぎ当てる
Excuse me. Could we please measure your Psycho-Pass?
失礼しまーす！
サイコパス測定にご協力お願いできますか
Whoa... It's looking pretty cloudy.
あらら　濁ってますね～
My assessment is that you require emergency therapy.
緊急セラピーを要するものと判断します
Please come with me.
ご同行願いますね
What? Why?
えっ　そんな…
I haven't done anything yet...
俺はまだ何も…
So you really can identify latent criminals?
本当に潜在犯の見分けがつくなんて…
With experience, you'll intuitively know at
first glance when someone's up to no good.
良からぬことを考えてるやつは
一目見ただけでピンとくるものさ
Committing crimes, or cracking down on them...
罪を犯すか　取り締まるか
Either way, they're talents that deal with criminal behavior.
どっちにしても犯罪に関わる才能であることに違いない
That's why my Crime Coefficient is so high.
だから俺なんかの犯罪係数もどえらい数値になっちまうのさ
Thanks to that, I'm now treated like
a hunting dog who gets all the dirty work.
おかげで今じゃ汚れ仕事を承る猟犬の扱いだ
In the end...
私　何の役にも立ってなかった
I was pretty useless in there, wasn't I?
No, you were quite helpful.
いや～大助かりだぜ
Enforcers can't walk around outside without an accompanying Inspector.
監視官同伴じゃなければ 執行官は外を出歩けねえんだから
But that's...
でも　それって…
We talked about this, right?
だからな…
After you bring Enforcers to the site,
執行官を現場まで連れてきて
all you need to do is keep an eye on them to make sure
they don't slack off, run away or cause trouble for society.
あとはサボったり逃げ出したり
世間さまにご迷惑がないようにしっかり見張る
That's all you need to do.
お嬢ちゃんの仕事はそれだけで十分なんだ
In other words, you're telling me not to do anything, right?
それってつまり　何も手出しをするなってことですよね
Can I join you, Ms. Inspector?
ご一緒していいっすか？監視官殿
Sure.
どうぞ
I thought you were already off duty today.
今日はもう非番なんじゃ…
We Enforcers are prisoners, you know.
俺ら執行官は捕らわれの身なんだぜ？
Even when we're off duty, there's nowhere else
we can go besides the CID floor and our quarters.
オフだって刑事課フロアと宿舎の他には行き場所なんかねえの
Well, sorry about earlier.
や～　昼間はごめんね
I got kinda carried away.
俺もついついはしゃいじゃってさ～
As you can see, all the other women who work here are scary as hell, so...
なんせここにいる女ときたらおっかねえやつばっかりだし
I'm just glad that a cute girl like you joined the CID, Akane.
朱ちゃんみたいなカワイイ子が来てくれて
すっげえうれしいっつうか…
Oh, can I call you Akane?
あっ　「朱ちゃん」って呼んでいい
Yeah, sure.
別にいいよ
But hell, an Inspector with the Public
Safety Bureau? Crazy place to work, right?
しっかしまあ 公安局監視官なんて
またとんでもない就職したもんだね
Why here?
何でまた？
Do you think I'm not suited for it?
向いてない…かな？
After what happened yesterday,
anyone would probably think that way.
昨日のあれを見たかぎりじゃね
誰だってそう思うんじゃない？
Sibyl's Judgment of my job aptitude
シビュラ判定の職能適性
exceeded the Bureau's employment standards, so here I am.
公安局の採用基準にパスできたから
That's the thing I don't get.
そこんとこ不思議なんだけどさ
If you passed the Bureau's standards,
公安局の基準を通ったんなら
you must've gotten a good ranking for other places too, right?
もっと他の適性もいい判定もらえてたんでしょ？
Couldn't you have picked a different job?
別の仕事だって選べたんじゃね？
Yeah.
うん…
I got an A ranking for all thirteen ministries
and agencies, not to mention six companies.
私ね　１３省庁６公司全部Ａ判定出たんだ
What?
えっ！？マジ？
S-Seriously?
Yeah. But...
うん…でもね
For all the other jobs, there were
at least one or two people besides me
他の仕事はどれも同じ判定をもらった子が
who got the same ranking.
私以外にも１人か２人はいたの
I was the only one who got an A ranking for the Public Safety Bureau.
公安局のＡ判定が出たのは私だけだった
There were more than 500 students and I was the only one.
５００人以上いた学生の中でただ一人私だけ
So I thought that there must have been
something that only I could do at the Bureau.
だから公安局にはね
私にしかできない仕事がきっとあるって思ってた
If I went there, I thought I could find my purpose in life...
そこに行けば本当の私の人生が…
I thought I'd be able to find out why I was born here and now.
この世界に生まれてきた意味が見つかるはずだって…
Do you think I'm wrong?
私の考え方間違ってるかな？
I don't know. What makes you think
that someone like me would have any idea?
分かんねえよ
俺なんかに分かるわけねえじゃん
You could become anything.
あんたは何にでもなれた
You could choose any kind of life.
どんな人生を選ぶことだってできた
You've even agonized over it, right?
それで悩みさえしたんだろ？
That's incredible.
すげえよな　まるでシビュラができる前のジジババみてえだ
You're just like those people from the days before Sibyl was created.
Nowadays, the Sibyl System reads your talent
今じゃシビュラシステムがそいつの才能を読み取って
and tells you the way of living that will bring you the most happiness.
一番幸せになれる生き方を教えてくれるってのに
And yet, you're talking about your purpose in life?
ホントの人生？生まれてきた意味？
The reason you were born?
I never even imagined there were
people who stressed over things like that!
そんなもんで悩むやつがいるなんて考えもしなかったよ
I was flagged in a Psycho-Pass test when I was five.
俺なんて５歳でサイコパス検診にはじかれて以来
I've been a latent criminal ever since.
ずーっと潜在犯だぜ
No possibility for rehabilitation through treatment.
治療更生の見込み　ゼロ
That's why I'm here now.
だから今俺はここにいる
And I'd much rather be one of the Bureau's hunting dogs
一生隔離施設で過ごすより公安局の猟犬になって
and take on assassination jobs than
spend the rest of my life in an isolation facility.
殺し屋稼業を引き受ける方がましだから
That was the only choice I had.
俺にはそれしかなかったからさ
I wasn't planning to be mean to you or anything,
俺　別にあんたに意地悪するつもりはなかったんだけどさ
but I changed my mind. So I'll ask you again.
気が変わったわ
だからあらためて聞いてやる
Why did you become an Inspector?
あんた　何で監視官なんかになったんだ
I'm so sorry!
すみませんでした
You don't see many Inspectors who'd apologize to an Enforcer.
執行官に謝る監視官は珍しい
I guess you're angry, right?
やっぱり　怒ってますか？
That was your decision.
あれがあんたの判断だった
I have no right to complain.
俺が文句を言える筋合いじゃない
Was my decision wrong?
私の判断間違ってたんでしょうか？
Did I just stand in everyone's way and put them in danger?
ただチームの足を引っ張って
みんなを危険にさらしただけだったんでしょうか？
I've been an Enforcer for a long time.
もう長いこと執行官をやっている
The hunting dogs' behavior of following orders
to take down prey with neither hesitation nor doubt
迷うことなく　疑うことなく
命じられたままに獲物を仕留める猟犬の習性が
is ingrained in my hands.
俺の手には染みついちまってる
I just followed that gun's orders,
あの銃の言いなりになって
and shot many latent criminals.
何人もの潜在犯を撃ってきた
It was for the good of society, I told myself.
それがこの社会のためになると
It was easier to just accept that logic without question,
小奇麗な理屈をうのみにして
and past a certain point I didn't even think about it anymore.
いつの間にか考えることさえなくなった
I didn't even think to look back at myself and what I was doing.
自分がやっていることが何なのか顧みることさえ忘れていた
I was a fool.
バカな話だ
Being a detective isn't about bringing people down.
デカってのは誰かを狩り取る仕事じゃなくて
It's supposed to be about protecting people.
誰かを守る仕事だったはずなのにな
Kougami...
狡噛さん…
You decided what was right on your own.
あんたは何が正しいかを自分で判断した
You were able to put justice before your duty.
役目より正義を優先できた
With a boss like you, I might be able
to work as a detective, not just a dog.
そういう上司の下なら
俺はただの犬ではなくデカとして働けるかもしれない
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございます
You also don't see many Inspectors who'd bow to an Enforcer.
執行官に礼を言う監視官も珍しい
If you had time to think about it with a level head,
もっと落ち着いて考える暇があったら
you would've tried not to shoot her, right?
狡噛さんだって彼女を撃とうとはしなかったですよね
I don't know.
どうだかな
I didn't hesitate at the time.
あのとき俺は迷わなかった
I thought I'd die if I hesitated.
迷えば死ぬと思っていた
I thought, "I don't want to die in a place like this.
こんなところで終わりたくない
I cannot die here, no matter what!"
絶対に　死ぬわけにはいかない
That one thought consumed me.
それだけで頭がいっぱいだった
I have unfinished business to take care of.
俺にはやり残したことがある
There's something I have to settle no matter what!
どうあっても　始末をつけなきゃならない役目が…
Kougami!
狡噛さん…
So, you're saying that you made the right decision at the time?
つまり　あの場における判断に間違いはなかったと…
Is that your conclusion, Inspector Tsunemori?
それが君の結論か？常守監視官
Yes. Her Crime Coefficient was only temporarily elevated.
はい　彼女の犯罪係数上昇は一過性のものでした
In fact, the therapy she's receiving after being taken into custody is going well,
事実　保護された後のセラピーも経過は良好で
and her Psycho-Pass is recovering.
サイコパスは回復に向かっています
Kougami, is there anything you want to say?
狡噛　何か言いたいことは？
No. Inspector Tsunemori fulfilled her duty.
ない
常守監視官は義務を果たした
That is all.
それだけだ
Fearii teeru wa
It seems all fairy tales
Sakki shinda mitai
Are dead
Renga no byoutou de
In a hospital ward of brick stones
Umaku utaenakute
My voice is too coarse to sing
Kiri ni kemuru yoru
Outside in the foggy haze
Ukabe akai tsuki
A red moon glows
Hora mite watashi wo
Look at me
Me wo sorasanai de
Do not avert your gaze
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
Behind black bars
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I was born
Behind black bars
Kuroi tetsu goushi no naka de
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
Akui no daishou wo negae
I wish there were a punishment for evil
I was born
Watashi wa umarete kitanda
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Always I need you
I wish there were a punishment for evil
Akui no daishou wo negae
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Now, grant us justice
Always I need you
Nozomu ga mama ni omae ni
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Before chaos takes us all
Now, grant us justice
Saa ataeyou seigi wo
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Before chaos takes us all
Kowashite kowasareru mae ni
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Namae no nai kaibutsu
Nameless beasts
Pay the price of fate and let us go together,
Inga no daishou wo harai tomo ni yukou
Nameless beasts
Namae no nai kaibutsu
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".